https://www.skydivecarolina.com/privacy/

Skydive Carolina(803) 581-JUMPGift CertificatesBook Now!First TimeTandem SkydivingPricesVideo ServicesReviewsFAQsLearn to SkydiveAccelerated Freefall CoursePricesFAQsExperienced SkydiversGeneral InfoEventsCarolinaFestLocal InfoPricesInfo & RatesGift CertificatesWho We AreOur StaffBlogDropzoneInformationAircraftEventsContactContact UsDirections
Skydive Carolina! is committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology that gives you the most powerful and safe online experience. This Statement of Privacy applies to the Skydive Carolina! Web site and governs data collection and usage. By using the Skydive Carolina! website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.Collection of your Personal InformationSkydive Carolina! collects personally identifiable information, such as your e-mail address, name, home or work address or telephone number. Skydive Carolina! also collects anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your ZIP code, age, gender, preferences, interests and favorites.There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by Skydive Carolina!. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring Web site addresses. This information is used by Skydive Carolina! for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Skydive Carolina! Web site.Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through Skydive Carolina! public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others. Note: Skydive Carolina! does not read any of your private online communications.Skydive Carolina! encourages you to review the privacy statements of Web sites you choose to link to from Skydive Carolina! so that you can understand how those Web sites collect, use and share your information. Skydive Carolina! is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on Web sites outside of the Skydive Carolina! and Skydive Carolina! family of Web sites.Use of your Personal InformationSkydive Carolina! collects and uses your personal information to operate the Skydive Carolina! Web site and deliver the services you have requested. Skydive Carolina! also uses your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from Skydive Carolina! and its affiliates. Skydive Carolina! may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.Skydive Carolina! does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. Skydive Carolina! may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. In addition, Skydive Carolina! may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Skydive Carolina!, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.Skydive Carolina! does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent.Skydive Carolina! keeps track of the Web sites and pages our customers visit within Skydive Carolina!, in order to determine what Skydive Carolina! services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within Skydive Carolina! to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.Skydive Carolina! Web sites will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Skydive Carolina! or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Skydive Carolina!; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Skydive Carolina!, or the public.Use of CookiesThe Skydive Carolina! Web site use “cookies” to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize Skydive Carolina! pages, or register with Skydive Carolina! site or services, a cookie helps Skydive Carolina! to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same Skydive Carolina! Web site, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the Skydive Carolina! features that you customized.You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Skydive Carolina! services or Web sites you visit.Security of your Personal InformationSkydive Carolina! secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. Skydive Carolina! secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other Web sites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.Changes to this StatementSkydive Carolina! will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. Skydive Carolina! encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Skydive Carolina! is protecting your information.Contact InformationSkydive Carolina! welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that Skydive Carolina! has not adhered to this Statement, please contact Skydive Carolina! at info@skydivecarolina.com We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.Stay ConnectedSign up to receive news and valuable promotions.First Name*Last Name*Email* PhoneThis field is for validation purposes and should be left unchanged.
Book Now!Copyright © 2020, Skydive Carolina, All Rights Reserved.DropZone Web Design & Marketing by Beyond Marketing, LLCBook Online Now!Buy Gift CertificatesContact Us (803) 581-JUMP 1903 King Air Dr •
Chester, SC 29706 | Direction Tips Friday: 10:00am - 6:00pm | Hours HomeFirst TimeTandem SkydivingPricesVideo ServicesReviewsFAQsLearn to SkydiveAccelerated Freefall CoursePricesFAQsExperienced SkydiversGeneral InfoEventsCarolinaFestLocal InfoPricesInfo & RatesGift CertificatesWho We AreOur StaffBlogDropzoneInformationAircraftEventsContactContact UsDirections We Know! We hate popups too!But this is totally worth it, because you could WIN a TANDEM SKYDIVE in our monthly drawing and receive some irregular e-mails offering you some sweet skydiving deals!
SUBSCRIBE!
You have Successfully Subscribed!
